Society of Protozoologists records
Society of Protozoologists records
- Series II. Executive Committee, 1947-1995; 439 folders (14.9 linear feet)
  - Sub-series II.C. Treasurer, 1965-1995; 230 folders (6 linear feet)
    - Financial/Invoices Paid 1994/7 - 1995/7 (Box 16, Folder 21)
    - Financial/Invoices Paid 1995/8 - 1996/6 (Box 16, Folder 22)
    - Financial/Invoices Paid 1996/7 - 1997/6 (Box 16, Folder 23)
    - Financial/Interest and Dividend Income 1993 (Box 16, Folder 24)
    - Financial/Journal 1970 - 1972 (Box 16, Folder 25)
    - Financial/Journal 1977 - 1981 (Box 16, Folder 26)
    - Financial/Journal (cash receipts) 1985/7 - 1986/6 (Box 16, Folder 27)
    - Financial/Journal of Protozoology (advertising) 1967/4 - 1970/4 (Box 16, Folder 28)
    - Financial/Journal of Protozoology Reprints 1965/1 - 1967/8 (Box 16, Folder 29)
    - Financial/Journal of Protozoology Reprints 1968/4 - 1970/5 (Box 16, Folder 30)
    - Financial/Journal of Protozoology 1969/4 - 1971/12 (Box 16, Folder 31)
    - Financial/Journal of Protozoology Webco Graphics 1967/1 - 1968/12 (Box 16, Folder 32)
    - Financial/Ledger 1984/7 - 1985/6 (Box 16, Folder 33)
    - Financial/Meeting (Bristol 1988) 1987/6 - 1989/5 (Box 17, Folder 1)
    - Financial/Meeting (Bloomington 1990) 1990/3 - 1990/12 (Box 17, Folder 2)
    - Financial/Meeting (Columbus 1990) 1990/9 - 1990/12 (Box 17, Folder 3)
    - Financial/Meeting (Cleveland 1994) 1994/7 (Box 17, Folder 4)
    - Financial/Recaps 1984/7 - 1984/10 (Box 17, Folder 5)
    - Financial/Recaps 1984/11 - 1984/12 (Box 17, Folder 6)
    - Financial/Recaps 1985/1 - 1985/3 (Box 17, Folder 7)
    - Financial/Recaps 1985/4 - 1985/6 (Box 17, Folder 8)
    - Financial/Recaps 1995/6 - 1995/12 (Box 17, Folder 9)
    - Financial/Recaps 1996/1 - 1996/6 (Box 17, Folder 10)
    - Financial/Recaps 1996/6 - 1996/12 (Box 17, Folder 11)
    - Financial/Recaps 1997/1 - 1997/6 (Box 17, Folder 12)
    - Financial/Recaps 1997/7 - 1997/12 (Box 17, Folder 13)
    - Financial/Recaps 1998/1 - 1998/6 (Box 17, Folder 14)
    - Financial/Special Publications 1982/1 - 1983/2 (Box 17, Folder 15)
    - Financial/Statement of Financial Condition 1980/7 - 1982/6 (Box 17, Folder 16)
    - Financial/Statement of Profit and Loss 1972/1975 (Box 17, Folder 17)
  - Subseries II.D. Tellers Committee, 1979-1992; 2 folders (.1 linear feet)
    Tellers Committee consists of ballots and election correspondence.
    - Ballots/1989 - 1992 (Box 17, Folder 18)
    - Correspondence/Election Results 1979 (Box 17, Folder 19)
- Series III. Membership., 1957-1991; 10 folders (2.65 linear feet)
  Membership files consist primarily of lists of members as well as groups of card files giving details of membership status.
  - Distribution Lists 1957 - 1959 (Box 17, Folder 20)
  - Honorary 1959 (Box 17, Folder 21)
  - Honorary Proposals 1968 - 1969 (Box 17, Folder 22)
  - Israeli Section 1972 (Box 17, Folder 23)
  - Lists 1971 - 1975 (Box 17, Folder 24)
  - List Book 1974 - 1981 (Box 17, Folder 25)
  - List 1980 (Box 17, Folder 26)
  - List Printout 1986 (Box 17, Folder 27)
  - Report 1989 - 1990 (Box 17, Folder 28)
  - Reports (Allen Press) 1988 - 1991 (Box 17, Folder 29)
  - Card File/1975 - 1983 (Box 18)
  - Card File/1983 Students, Non US, ԍiscellaneous Oldies" (Box 19)
- Series IV. Meetings, 1953-1990; 69 folders (1.5 linear feet)
  The Meetings Series is divided into two subseries: Annual Business/Membership meetings and Executive Committee meetings. They are arranged in date order. Materials included vary and may contain correspondence, minutes, reports and arrangements.
  - Subseries IV.A. Annual Business/Membership, 1953-1990; 38 folders (.75 linear feet)
    Annual Business/Membership (used interchangeably) are in date order. International meetings are also listed in this group. The files may include minutes of the meetings, reports, correspondence and arrangements.
    - 1953 (Madison Wi.) (Box 20, Folder 1)
    - 1954 (Gainesville, Fl.) (Box 20, Folder 2)
    - 1955 (Lansing, Mi.) (Box 20, Folder 3)
    - 1956 (Storrs, Ct.) (Box 20, Folder 4)
    - 1957 (Stanford, Ca.) (Box 20, Folder 5)
    - 1958 (Bloomington, Ind.) (Box 20, Folder 6)
    - 1959 (University Park, Pa.) (Box 20, Folder 7)
    - 1960 (Stillwater, Ok.) (Box 20, Folder 8)
    - 1961 (Denver, Co.) (Box 20, Folder 9)
    - 1962 (Corvallis, Or.) (Box 20, Folder 10)
    - 1963 (Amherst, Ma.) (Box 20, Folder 11)
    - 1964 (Boulder, Co.) (Box 20, Folder 12)
    - 1965 (London, England) (Box 20, Folder 13)
    - 1966 (College Park, Md.) (Box 20, Folder 14)
    - 1967 (Toronto, Canada) (Box 20, Folder 15)
    - 1968 (Columbus, Oh.) (Box 20, Folder 16)
    - 1969 (Boston, Ma.) (Box 20, Folder 17)
    - 1970 (Washington, D.C.) (Box 20, Folder 18)
    - 1971 (Ft. Collins, Co. ) (Box 20, Folder 19)
    - 1972 (Minneapolis, Mn.) (Box 20, Folder 20)
    - 1973 (Clerant-Ferrand, France) (Box 20, Folder 21)
    - 1973 (Houston, Tx.) (Box 20, Folder 22)
    - 1974 (Middletown, Ct.) (Box 20, Folder 23)
    - 1975 (Corvallis, Or.) (Box 20, Folder 24)
    - 1976 (New Orleans, La.) (Box 20, Folder 25)
    - 1977 (New York, N.Y.) (Box 20, Folder 26)
    - 1978 (Athens, Ga.) (Box 20, Folder 27)
    - 1979 (Stillwater, Ok.) (Box 20, Folder 28)
    - 1980 (Washington, D.C.) (Box 20, Folder 29)
    - 1981 (Dallas, Tx.) (Box 20, Folder 30)
    - 1982 ( San Francisco, Ca.) (Box 20, Folder 31)
    - 1983 (New York, N. Y.) (Box 20, Folder 32)
    - 1984 (Athens, Ga.) (Box 20, Folder 33)
    - 1985 (Nairobi, Kenya) (Box 20, Folder 34)
    - 1986 (Kingston, R.I.) (Box 20, Folder 35)
    - 1987 (Champaign-Urbana, Il.) (Box 20, Folder 36)
    - 1989 (Tsukuba, Japan) (Box 20, Folder 37)
    - 1990 ( College Park, Md.) (Box 20, Folder 38)
  - Subseries IV.B. Executive Committee, 1954-1990; 31 folders (.75 linear feet)
    The Executive Committee meetings are generally held in conjunction with the annual business/membership meetings, although occasionally they are held at other times. They are listed in date order. Materials in the folders may contain meeting minutes, arrangements and correspondence.
    - 1954, 1955, 1956, 1959, 1960, 1961 (Box 20, Folder 39)
    - 1962, 1963 (Box 20, Folder 40)
    - 1964 (Boulder, Co.) (Box 20, Folder 41)
    - 1965 (London, England) (Box 20, Folder 42)
    - 1966 (College Park, Md.) (Box 20, Folder 43)
    - 1967 (Toronto, Canada) (Box 20, Folder 44)
    - 1968 (Columbus, Oh.) (Box 20, Folder 45)
    - 1969 (Boston, Ma.) (Box 20, Folder 46)
    - 1970 (Washington, D.C.) (Box 20, Folder 47)
    - 1971 (Ft. Collins, Co.) (Box 20, Folder 48)
    - 1972 (Minneapolis, Mn.) (Box 20, Folder 49)
    - 1973 (Clermont, France) (Box 20, Folder 50)
    - 1973 (Houston, Tx.) (Box 20, Folder 51)
    - 1974 (Stillwater, Ok.) (Box 20, Folder 52)
    - 1975 ( Corvallis, Or.) (Box 20, Folder 53)
    - 1976 (New Orleans, La.) (Box 20, Folder 54)
    - 1977 (New York, N.Y.) (Box 20, Folder 55)
    - 1978 (Athens, Ga.) (Box 20, Folder 56)
    - 1979 (Stillwater, Ok.) (Box 21, Folder 1)
    - 1980 (Washington, D.C.) (Box 21, Folder 2)
    - 1981 (Dallas, Tx.) (Box 21, Folder 3)
    - 1981 (Warsaw, Poland) (Box 21, Folder 4)
    - 1982 (San Francisco, Ca.) (Box 21, Folder 5)
    - 1983 (New York, N.Y.) (Box 21, Folder 6)
    - 1984 (Athens, Ga.) (Box 21, Folder 7)
    - 1985 (Cincinnati, Oh. and Nairobi, Kenya) (Box 21, Folder 8)
    - 1986 (College Park, Md. and Kingston, R.I.) (Box 21, Folder 9)
    - 1987 (Champaign-Urbana, Il.) (Box 21, Folder 10)
    - 1988 (Bristol, England) (Box 21, Folder 11)
    - 1989 (Tsukuba, Japan) (Box 21, Folder 12)
    - 1990 (College Park, Md.) (Box 21, Folder 13)
- Series V. Publications, 1954- 2012; 30 folders (8.25 linear feet)
  Files are arranged by the type of publication and then in date order.
  - Careers in Protozoology/1970 (Box 21, Folder 14)
  - Illustrated Guide to Protozoa (Box 21, Folder 15)
  - Journal of Protozoology/Editor List 1968 - 1978 (Box 21, Folder 16)
  - Journal of Protozoology 1969 (Box 21, Folder 17)
  - Journal of Protozoology/Abstracts 1962 (Box 21, Folder 18)
  - Journal of Protozoology/Advertising 1958 - 1962 (Box 21, Folder 19)
  - Journal of Protozoology/Advertising 1973 - 1979 (Box 21, Folder 20)
  - Journal of Protozoology/Allen Press (Abstracts) 1985 - 1986 (Box 21, Folder 21)
  - Journal of Protozoology/Allen Press (National Periodical Center) 1980 (Box 21, Folder 22)
  - Journal of Protozoology/Allen Press (Subscriptions Received) 1988 - 1990 (Box 21, Folder 23)
  - Journal of Protozoology/Article Reviews 1969 - 1973 (Box 21, Folder 24)
  - Journal of Protozoology/Board of Reviews 1988 - 1990 (Box 21, Folder 25)
  - Journal of Protozoology/Correspondence 1982 - 1983 (Box 21, Folder 26)
  - Journal of Protozoology/Cover 1986 - 1989 (Box 21, Folder 27)
  - Journal of Protozoology/Cover Design 1986 (Box 21, Folder 28)
  - Journal of Protozoology/Expenses 1967 - 1970 (Box 21, Folder 29)
  - Journal of Protozoology/Meeting 1988/3 (Box 21, Folder 30)
  - Journal of Protozoology/Purchase Orders 1967 - 1970 (Box 21, Folder 31)
  - Journal of Protozoology/Programs and Abstracts 1972/8 - 1972/9 (Box 21, Folder 32)
  - Journal of Protozoology/Supplement (Membership List) 1989 (Box 21, Folder 33)
  - Journal of Eukaryotic Microbiology/Finances 1991-2012 (Box 21, Folder 34)
  - Journal of Eukaryotic Microbiology/Annual Reports, 2001, 2005 (Box 21, Folder 35)
  - Journal of Eukaryotic Microbiology/Report to Executive Committee 2003 (Box 21, Folder 36)
  - Meetings/Programs 1980, 1983, 1984 (Box 21, Folder 37)
  - Meetings/Programs 1985, 1986 (Box 21, Folder 38)
  - Meetings/Programs and Abstracts 1992 (Box 21, Folder 39)
  - Newsletter 1951 (Box 21, Folder 40)
  - Newsletters 1970 - 1983 (not complete) (Box 21, Folder 41)
  - Newsletters 1984 - 1987 (not complete) (Box 21, Folder 42)
  - Newsletters 1991 - 1993 (not complete) (Box 21, Folder 43)
  - Newsletters/British Section 1989 (Box 21, Folder 44)
  - So You Want To Be A Protozoologist? (Box 21, Folder 45)
  - Symposium and Workshop 1992 (Box 21, Folder 46)
  - Volumes/Bound (Journal of Protozoology) Vol I 1954 - Vol XIII 1966 (Box 22)
  - Volumes/Bound (Journal of Protozoology) Vol XIV 1967 - Vol XXI 1974 (Box 23)
  - Volumes/Bound (Journal of Protozoology) Vol XXII 1975 - Vol XXIX 1982 (Box 24)
  - Volumes/Bound (Journal of Protozoology) Vol XXX 1983 - Vol XXXVII 1990 (Box 25)
  - Volumes/Bound (Journal of Protozoology) Vol XXXVIII 1991 - Vol XXXIX 1992, (Journal of Eukaryotic Microbiology) Vol XL 1993 - Vol XLI 1994 (Box 26)
- Series VI. Affiliated Societies, 1953-1982; 9 folders (.25 linear feet)
  The Affiliated Societies files are arranged in alpha order and then in date order.
  - Agricultural Research Institute 1953 - 1958 (Box 27, Folder 1)
  - American Association for the Advancement of Science/Meeting 1960 (New York) (Box 27, Folder 2)
  - American Institute of Biological Sciences (Box 27, Folder 3)
  - American Society for Cell Biology/Meeting 1970 (Box 27, Folder 4)
  - American Society for Cell Biology/Meeting 1974 (Box 27, Folder 5)
  - American Type Culture Collection (Box 27, Folder 6)
  - National Academy of Sciences 1956 - 1964 (Box 27, Folder 7)
  - Technical and Scientific Societies of the United States/Future Scientists of America Awards 1961 ֱ962 (Box 27, Folder 8)
  - World Federation of Parasitologists/ 1978 - 1982 (Box 27, Folder 9)
- Series VII. Miscellaneous, 1958-1986; 13 folders (.5 linear feet)
  Files are arranged by format.
  - Correspondence 1958 - 1986 (Box 27, Folder 10)
  - Photographs (unmarked and not dated) (Box 27, Folder 11)
  - Photographs (unmarked and not dated) (Box 27, Folder 12)
  - Photographs (unmarked and not dated) (Box 27, Folder 13)
  - Photographs (unmarked and not dated) (Box 27, Folder 14)
  - Photographs (unmarked/1987) (Box 27, Folder 15)
  - Recording Tape (unmarked and not dated) (Box 28, Folder 1)
  - Recording Tape/Executive Committee Meeting 1963/8 Reel 1 (Box 28, Folder 2)
  - Recording Tape/Executive Committee Meeting 1963/8 Reel 2 (Box 28, Folder 3)
  - Floppy Disks-5ԯHofstra Meeting Remarks and Report (Box 28, Folder 4)
  - Slide Collection of Eugene Bovee (Box 28, Folder 5)
  - Logo Art Work (Box 28, Folder 6)
  - Award Art Work (Box 28, Folder 7)
- Addendum 1. Series II. Executive Committee
  - Subseries II.C. Treasurer, 1989-2000; 124 folders (3 linear feet)
    This addendum contains financial records. The majority are receipt ledgers and income statements. There is a complete monthly run from 1990/7 to 2000/6. The files are in alpha order followed by date order.
    - Financial/Business Advisory Committee Report 1994 (Box 29, Folder 1)
    - Financial/Internal Revenue Forms 1099 1989, 1990 (Box 29, Folder 2)
    - Financial/Internal Revenue Forms 1099 1991, 1993, 1994 (Box 29, Folder 3)
    - Financial/Internal Revenue Forms 1096 1993, 1994 (Box 29, Folder 4)
    - Financial/Receipts Ledger & Income Statements 1990/7 (Box 29, Folder 5)
    - Financial/Receipts Ledger & Income Statements 1990/8 (Box 29, Folder 6)
    - Financial/Receipts Ledger & Income Statements 1990/9 (Box 29, Folder 7)
    - Financial/Receipts Ledger & Income Statements 1990/10 (Box 29, Folder 8)
    - Financial/Receipts Ledger & Income Statements 1990/11 (Box 29, Folder 9)
    - Financial/Receipts Ledger & Income Statements 1990/12 (Box 29, Folder 10)
    - Financial/Receipts Ledger & Income Statements 1991/1 (Box 29, Folder 11)
    - Financial/Receipts Ledger & Income Statements 1991/2 (Box 29, Folder 12)
    - Financial/Receipts Ledger & Income Statements 1991/3 (Box 29, Folder 13)
    - Financial/Receipts Ledger & Income Statements 1991/4 (Box 29, Folder 14)
    - Financial/Receipts Ledger & Income Statements 1991/5 (Box 29, Folder 15)
    - Financial/Receipts Ledger & Income Statements 1991/6 (Box 29, Folder 16)
    - Financial/Receipts Ledger & Income Statements 1991/7 (Box 29, Folder 17)
    - Financial/Receipts Ledger & Income Statements 1991/8 (Box 29, Folder 18)
    - Financial/Receipts Ledger & Income Statements 1991/9 (Box 29, Folder 19)
    - Financial/Receipts Ledger & Income Statements 1991/10 (Box 29, Folder 20)
    - Financial/Receipts Ledger & Income Statements 1991/11 (Box 29, Folder 21)
    - Financial/Receipts Ledger & Income Statements 1991/12 (Box 29, Folder 22)
    - Financial/Receipts Ledger & Income Statements 1992/1 (Box 29, Folder 23)
    - Financial/Receipts Ledger & Income Statements 1992/2 (Box 29, Folder 24)
    - Financial/Receipts Ledger & Income Statements 1992/3 (Box 29, Folder 25)
    - Financial/Receipts Ledger & Income Statements 1992/4 (Box 29, Folder 26)
    - Financial/Receipts Ledger & Income Statements 1992/5 (Box 29, Folder 27)
    - Financial/Receipts Ledger & Income Statements 1992/6 (Box 29, Folder 28)
    - Financial/Receipts Ledger & Income Statements 1992/7 (Box 29, Folder 29)
    - Financial/Receipts Ledger & Income Statements 1992/8 (Box 29, Folder 30)
    - Financial/Receipts Ledger & Income Statements 1992/9 (Box 29, Folder 31)
    - Financial/Receipts Ledger & Income Statements 1992/10 (Box 29, Folder 32)
    - Financial/Receipts Ledger & Income Statements 1992/11 (Box 29, Folder 33)
    - Financial/Receipts Ledger & Income Statements 1992/12 (Box 29, Folder 34)
    - Financial/Receipts Ledger & Income Statements 1993/1 (Box 29, Folder 35)
    - Financial/Receipts Ledger & Income Statements 1993/2 (Box 29, Folder 36)
    - Financial/Receipts Ledger & Income Statements 1993/3 (Box 29, Folder 37)
    - Financial/Receipts Ledger & Income Statements 1993/4 (Box 29, Folder 38)
    - Financial/Receipts Ledger & Income Statements 1993/5 (Box 29, Folder 39)
    - Financial/Receipts Ledger & Income Statements 1993/6 (Box 29, Folder 40)
    - Financial/Receipts Ledger & Income Statements 1993/7 (Box 29, Folder 41)
    - Financial/Receipts Ledger & Income Statements 1993/8 (Box 29, Folder 42)
    - Financial/Receipts Ledger & Income Statements 1993/9 (Box 29, Folder 43)
    - Financial/Receipts Ledger & Income Statements 1993/10 (Box 29, Folder 44)
    - Financial/Receipts Ledger & Income Statements 1993/11 (Box 29, Folder 45)
    - Financial/Receipts Ledger & Income Statements 1993/12 (Box 29, Folder 46)
    - Financial/Receipts Ledger & Income Statements 1994/1 (Box 29, Folder 47)
    - Financial/Receipts Ledger & Income Statements 1994/2 (Box 29, Folder 48)
    - Financial/Receipts Ledger & Income Statements 1994/3 (Box 29, Folder 49)
    - Financial/Receipts Ledger & Income Statements 1994/4 (Box 29, Folder 50)
    - Financial/Receipts Ledger & Income Statements 1994/5 (Box 29, Folder 51)
    - Financial/Receipts Ledger & Income Statements 1994/6 (Box 29, Folder 52)
    - Financial/Receipts Ledger & Income Statements 1994/7 (Box 29, Folder 53)
    - Financial/Receipts Ledger & Income Statements 1994/8 (Box 29, Folder 54)
    - Financial/Receipts Ledger & Income Statements 1994/9 (Box 29, Folder 55)
    - Financial/Receipts Ledger & Income Statements 1994/10 (Box 29, Folder 56)
    - Financial/Receipts Ledger & Income Statements 1994/11 (Box 29, Folder 57)
    - Financial/Receipts Ledger & Income Statements 1994/12 (Box 29, Folder 58)
    - Financial/Receipts Ledger & Income Statements 1995/1 (Box 29, Folder 59)
    - Financial/Receipts Ledger & Income Statements 1995/2 (Box 29, Folder 60)
    - Financial/Receipts Ledger & Income Statements 1995/3 (Box 29, Folder 61)
    - Financial/Receipts Ledger & Income Statements 1995/4 (Box 29, Folder 62)
    - Financial/Receipts Ledger & Income Statements 1995/5 (Box 29, Folder 63)
    - Financial/Receipts Ledger & Income Statements 1995/6 (Box 29, Folder 64)
    - Financial/Receipts Ledger & Income Statements 1995/7 (Box 29, Folder 65)
    - Financial/Receipts Ledger & Income Statements 1995/8 (Box 29, Folder 66)
    - Financial/Receipts Ledger & Income Statements 1995/9 (Box 29, Folder 67)
    - Financial/Receipts Ledger & Income Statements 1995/10 (Box 29, Folder 68)
    - Financial/Receipts Ledger & Income Statements 1995/11 (Box 29, Folder 69)
    - Financial/Receipts Ledger & Income Statements 1995/12 (Box 29, Folder 70)
    - Financial/Receipts Ledger & Income Statements 1996/1 (Box 30, Folder 1)
    - Financial/Receipts Ledger & Income Statements 1996/2 (Box 30, Folder 2)
    - Financial/Receipts Ledger & Income Statements 1996/3 (Box 30, Folder 3)
    - Financial/Receipts Ledger & Income Statements 1996/4 (Box 30, Folder 4)
    - Financial/Receipts Ledger & Income Statements 1996/5 (Box 30, Folder 5)
    - Financial/Receipts Ledger & Income Statements 1996/6 (Box 30, Folder 6)
    - Financial/Receipts Ledger & Income Statements 1996/7 (Box 30, Folder 7)
    - Financial/Receipts Ledger & Income Statements 1996/8 (Box 30, Folder 8)
    - Financial/Receipts Ledger & Income Statements 1996/9 (Box 30, Folder 9)
    - Financial/Receipts Ledger & Income Statements 1996/10 (Box 30, Folder 10)
    - Financial/Receipts Ledger & Income Statements 1996/11 (Box 30, Folder 11)
    - Financial/Receipts Ledger & Income Statements 1996/12 (Box 30, Folder 12)
    - Financial/Receipts Ledger & Income Statements 1997/1 (Box 30, Folder 13)
    - Financial/Receipts Ledger & Income Statements 1997/2 (Box 30, Folder 14)
    - Financial/Receipts Ledger & Income Statements 1997/3 (Box 30, Folder 15)
    - Financial/Receipts Ledger & Income Statements 1997/4 (Box 30, Folder 16)
    - Financial/Receipts Ledger & Income Statements 1997/5 (Box 30, Folder 17)
    - Financial/Receipts Ledger & Income Statements 1997/6 (Box 30, Folder 18)
    - Financial/Receipts Ledger & Income Statements 1997/7 (Box 30, Folder 19)
    - Financial/Receipts Ledger & Income Statements 1997/8 (Box 30, Folder 20)
    - Financial/Receipts Ledger & Income Statements 1997/9 (Box 30, Folder 21)
    - Financial/Receipts Ledger & Income Statements 1997/10 (Box 30, Folder 22)
    - Financial/Receipts Ledger & Income Statements 1997/11 (Box 30, Folder 23)
    - Financial/Receipts Ledger & Income Statements 1997/12 (Box 30, Folder 24)
    - Financial/Receipts Ledger & Income Statements 1998/1 (Box 30, Folder 25)
    - Financial/Receipts Ledger & Income Statements 1998/2 (Box 30, Folder 26)
    - Financial/Receipts Ledger & Income Statements 1998/3 (Box 30, Folder 27)
    - Financial/Receipts Ledger & Income Statements 1998/4 (Box 30, Folder 28)
    - Financial/Receipts Ledger & Income Statements 1998/5 (Box 30, Folder 29)
    - Financial/Receipts Ledger & Income Statements 1998/6 (Box 30, Folder 30)
    - Financial/Receipts Ledger & Income Statements 1998/7 (Box 30, Folder 31)
    - Financial/Receipts Ledger & Income Statements 1998/8 (Box 30, Folder 32)
    - Financial/Receipts Ledger & Income Statements 1998/9 (Box 30, Folder 33)
    - Financial/Receipts Ledger & Income Statements 1998/10 (Box 30, Folder 34)
    - Financial/Receipts Ledger & Income Statements 1998/11 (Box 30, Folder 35)
    - Financial/Receipts Ledger & Income Statements 1998/12 (Box 30, Folder 36)
    - Financial/Receipts Ledger & Income Statements 1999/1 (Box 30, Folder 37)
    - Financial/Receipts Ledger & Income Statements 1999/2 (Box 30, Folder 38)
    - Financial/Receipts Ledger & Income Statements 1999/3 (Box 30, Folder 39)
    - Financial/Receipts Ledger & Income Statements 1999/4 (Box 30, Folder 40)
    - Financial/Receipts Ledger & Income Statements 1999/5 (Box 30, Folder 41)
    - Financial/Receipts Ledger & Income Statements 1999/6 (Box 30, Folder 42)
    - Financial/Receipts Ledger & Income Statements 1999/7 (Box 30, Folder 43)
    - Financial/Receipts Ledger & Income Statements 1999/8 (Box 30, Folder 44)
    - Financial/Receipts Ledger & Income Statements 1999/9 (Box 30, Folder 45)
    - Financial/Receipts Ledger & Income Statements 1999/10 (Box 30, Folder 46)
    - Financial/Receipts Ledger & Income Statements 1999/11 (Box 30, Folder 47)
    - Financial/Receipts Ledger & Income Statements 1999/12 (Box 30, Folder 48)
    - Financial/Receipts Ledger & Income Statements 2000/1 (Box 30, Folder 49)
    - Financial/Receipts Ledger & Income Statements 2000/2 (Box 30, Folder 50)
    - Financial/Receipts Ledger & Income Statements 2000/3 (Box 30, Folder 51)
    - Financial/Receipts Ledger & Income Statements 2000/4 (Box 30, Folder 52)
    - Financial/Receipts Ledger & Income Statements 2000/5 (Box 30, Folder 53)
    - Financial/Receipts Ledger & Income Statements 2000/6 (Box 30, Folder 54)